Guide to the Edgar A. Prichard papers, 1962-1981
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Edgar A. Prichard papers
1962-1981
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Edgar A. Prichard
C0156
14.25 linear feet (29 boxes)
The Edgar A. Prichard papers include correspondence, legal, finance and other papers relating to Reston. The majority of the collection deals with property, dedications, deeds, sales and leases in Reston. The documents are primarily from Prichard's dealing with the Palindrome Corporation and Gulf Reston Incorporated.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Edgar A. Prichard in December 1990.
Biographical Information
Reston is a planned community in Northern Virginia. Robert E. Simon, Jr., the founder of Reston, purchased the land with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. In 1967, Gulf Oil Corporation formed a subsidiary, Reston Gulf Incorporated and took complete financial and operational control. Reston Gulf Incorporated continued the growing development. When the Mobil Corporation bought the remaining undeveloped land from Gulf Reston in 1978, Reston Land Corporation (RLC) was formed as a subsidiary. From Reston's early development in the 1960s through the establishment of the RLC, attorney Edgar A. Prichard participated in many legal, financial, and property transactions.
Scope and Content
The Edgar A. Prichard papers include correspondence, legal, finance and other papers relating to Reston. The majority of the collection deals with property, dedications, deeds, sales and leases in Reston. The documents are primarily from Prichard's dealing with the Palindrome Corporation and Gulf Reston Incorporated. The collection is divided into nines series in 28 document cases and is dated from 1962 to 1981.
Series one contains correspondence dated from 1962 to 1969. The correspondence is mostly memoranda between Edgar A. Prichard and other corporations concerning different buildings, primarily residential buildings, in Reston. The series is relatively small and is contained in boxes 1 and 2.
Series two consists of information on different project in Reston. The information in this series involves building projects such as the First Village Center, Lake Anne Nursery, the swim and tennis club and other projects in Reston. The series is dated from 1965 to 1969 and is contained in boxes 3 and 4.
Series three is a collection of deeds of dedications and rededications from Reston. The dedications are from resubdivisions, amendments, roads and other places in Reston. The series is dated from 1962 to 1969. The series is contained within three boxes 5 through 6.
Series four contains financial papers. The series has tax, loans, foreclosures and apartment financing information relating to the development of Reston in the 1960s. The series is dated from 1964 to 1968 and contained within boxes 6 through 9.
Series five consists of paperwork from different organizations in Reston such as the Reston Home Owners Association and the Palindrome Corporation. The series is dated from 1962 to 1968 and is contained within boxes 9 through 12.
Series six consists mostly of information on different court cases that Edgar A. Prichard was working on behalf of Reston. There are several files involving Gulf Reston, Incorporated vs. Board of Supervisors Stipulations in the 1970s and the US District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia. The series is dated from 1965 to 1978 and is stored in boxes 12 through 16.
Series seven contains contracts with different organizations, such as the Catholic Church in Fairfax, Motorola, Eugene Simpson and Brothers, Incorporated on the Lakeview Contract and various others. The series is dated from 1964 to 1968 and is stored in boxes 16 through 19.
Series eight contains paperwork from various sales throughout Reston, including lots, homes and space from different corporations. Also in the series are documents from repurchased area. The series is dated from 1964 to 1971 and is stored in boxes 19 through 23.
Series nine has a variety of different documents covering a variety of topics. Some of those topics include restriction files, parking, telephone numbers, advertisements and resubdivisions. The series is dated from 1962 to 1981 and is stored in boxes 24 through 29.
Arrangement
Organized into nine series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 1-2)
Series 2: Projects, 1964-1969 (Boxes 3-4)
Series 3: Dedications, 1962-1969 (Boxes 5-6)
Series 4: Finances, 1964-1968 (Boxes 6-9)
Series 5: Associations and Corporations, 1962-1968 (Boxes 9-12)
Series 6: Legal Files, 1965-1978 (Boxes 12-16)
Series 7: Contracts, 1964-1968 (Boxes 16-19)
Series 8: Sales, 1964-1971 (Boxes 19-23)
Series 9: General Information, 1962-1981 (Boxes 24-29)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Persons:
Prichard, Edgar A.
Corporate Names:
Gulf Reston, Inc.; Palindrome Corporation; Reston Land Corporation
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing--Virginia--Reston.; Planned communities--Virginia--Reston.
Contents List
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1965-1969; (2 boxes)
  Series one is correspondence in boxes 1 and 2. The correspondence is mostly memorandas between Edgar A. Prichard and other corporations
  - Palindrome Corporation Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    210.8
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    376.11
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Vacancy and Reusable Lots of 14-21, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    376.10
  - Western Waterproofing Company and Maintenance Bond, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    377.3
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Garnishments on Wages General File, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    376.12
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Resubdivision of Block 18, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    376.4
  - Vacancy and Rededication of Lots 11, 12 and 13, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    375.1
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Block 15, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    374.10
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Collection defense, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    374.8
  - Palindrome Corporation Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    210.7
  - Removal of Gables, Section 6, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    374.3
  - Tax Opinion and Employment Service Licensing Requirements, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    382.7
  - Town of Herndon Sewer Easement, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    383.11
  - Edward F. Sullivan, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    381.9
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Storm Sewer and Drainage Easements, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    378.8
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Storm Sewer Easements, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Edgar Prichard and Daniel McArver: Open Flower Stall and Plaza Licensing Problems, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    380.8
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    383.15
  - Reusable and Rededication of Block 135, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    384.3
  - Sewer Easement over Sugarland Run, Herndon, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    384.4
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: New Town Legislation, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    384.11
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Lakeview Mall Associates (Jack Houston), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    387.2
  - Progress Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    390.16
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Schultz-Farway Apartments East, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    393.4
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Schultz-Fairway Apartments West, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    393.5
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Open Space Problems, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    393.15
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Schultz Construction Corporation Miscellaneous File, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    393.2
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Advertisements, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    388.7
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Lynn Bartle-Garnishment and Prior Employment Record, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    387.8
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Crossing Permits, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    387.9
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Warehousing Arrangement with Bankers Jr. and Vienna Jr., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    387.10
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Warrants Claims, Mr. and Mrs. Albert Jankowitz, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    391.10
  - Gulf Reston Incorporated: Klingbeil (Khempco Property Sales Company 29 Townhouses in Governor's Square), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    391.7
  - Lake Wall Lawsuit, Whittlesey at Conklin, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    391.2
  - Lake Wall Lawsuit, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    391.1
  - Internal Correspondence, Protective Covenants, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    210.6
- Series 2: Projects, 1965-1969; (2 boxes)
  Series two is titled Projects. The information in this series involves building projects such as, the First Village Center, Lake Anne Nursery and others. The series is stored in boxes 3 and 4.
  - Gulf Service Station Site, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    367.10
  - Lynch Edwin Trustee for Vernon M. Lunch Sons: Plantations Pipe Line Company, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    366.6
  - Emergency Rezoning of Industrial Land for used by Motorola, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    366.7
  - Rezoning Application to Reston Palindrome Corporation 146 Acres, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    369.3
  - Rezoning Balance of Independent Zone, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    368.4
  - Specification for First Village Center, Phase 2, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    366.2
  - Specifications for First Village Center, Phase 2, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    366.3
  - First Village Center, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    366.4
  - Lake Anne Nursery School, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    370.12
    - Lake Anne Nursery-Kindergarten (Planning report), pre-1965?; 1.
  - Lake Anne Community Center, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    370.11
  - Voluntary Dissolution of Swim and Tennis Clubs, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    373.6
  - Golf Course Island, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    377.1
  - A.P. Woodson, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    371.6
  - Golf Course Island, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lease of Bowman Chapel, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    379.1
  - Armce Steele Company-East Coast Center, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    383.2
  - Membership of Reston Pools in Northern Virginia Swimming League, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    379.8
  - Reston Park Incorporated, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    379.2
    - Reston Park, Inc., Attachment to From 1023 Exemption Application, 1967; 1.
  - Rezoning Application, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    383.1
  - Part of Parcel 15A, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    478.6
  - Master Copy of First Village Center REcord of Construction, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    478.4
  - Summary of the Record of Construction of the First Village Center, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    366.1
- Series 3: Dedications, 1962-1969; (2 boxes)
  Series three is titled Dedications. The dedications are from amendments and other places in Reston. The series is stored in boxes 4 through 6.
  - Deed of Dedication File, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    211.2
  - Deed of Dedication, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    211.6
  - Deed of Dedication, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    210.9
  - Deed of Dedication File, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    211.1
  - Plat and Deed of Dedication, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    368.2
    - Deed of Dedication (Draft - Widening of Routes 602 and 667), October 1964; 1.
  - Deed of Dedication and Plats Widening, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    368.10
  - Deed of Vacation and Rededication, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    369.5
  - Vacation and Rededication of Route 673 (Lawyers Road), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    370.5
    - Deed of Dedication (Copy - Vacation and Rededication of Route 673, Lawyers Rd), June 28, 1965; 1.
  - Deed of Dedication For Widening Route 602, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    370.6
    - Deed of Dedication (Copy - Widening of route 602), July 15, 1965; 1.
  - Parcel 14 Rededication, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    370.15
  - Dedication of Second Extension of North Shore Drive, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    371.3
  - Deed of Dedication of Section Three, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    371.4
  - Amendment to Deed of Dedication, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    372.8
  - Deed of Dedication Section 4-B and Addition to Section 4, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    372.12
  - Deed of Dedication of Section 6, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    374.4
  - Deed of Dedication of Section 5, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    374.5
  - Deed of Dedication of Section 2, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    376.8
  - Rededication of Section 7, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    378.7
  - Repurchase of Dedication of Extension of Widhle Avenue Through Parcel 4, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    378.4
  - Dedication of Section 15, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    389.9
  - Deed of Resubdivision and Rededication and Easement Agreement, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    390.5
  - Deed of Dedication of Storm Sewer Casements, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    390.6
  - Deed of Dedication, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    210.5
- Series 4: Finance, 1964-1968; (3 boxes)
  Series four are financial papers such as loans and apartment financing information. The series is stored in boxes 6 through 9.
  - Berger Loan to Palindrome, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    369.4
  - State Planters Loan to Reston, Virginia, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    479.2
  - Financing Statement, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    376.2
  - Refinancing, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    377.5
  - Tax Exemption for Home Owner and Cluster Assignments and Swim and Tennis Clubs, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    373.1
  - Loan for Hazelton Building, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    380.5
  - Hancock/Gulf Apartment Financing, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    378.1
  - Hancock/Gulf Apartment Financing, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    377.9
  - Hancock/Gulf Apartment Financing, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    377.7
  - Hancock/Gulf Apartment Financing, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    377.10
  - Loan to Willa Investment Corporation, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    386.5
  - General Technology, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    381.1
  - General Technology, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    382.2
  - Reston Incorporated, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    380.10
  - Reston Incorporated, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    380.11
  - Reston Incorporated, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    380.9
  - Foreclosure v. Allen Townhouse Corporated, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    383.7
  - Foreclosures by Arlington Trust Company, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    383.8
  - Foreclosure-Reynolds Construction Corporation, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    382.9
  - Foreclosure on Lots 36 and 38, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    386.9
  - Virginia Insured Financing, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    393.1
  - State Planters Loan to Reston, Virginia, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    479.5
  - State Planters Loan To Reston, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    479.4
  - Reston Loans Sold to National Bank of Fairfax, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    479.3
  - State Planters Loan to Reston, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    478.7
  - State Planters Loan to Reston, Virginia, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    479.1
  - Investment Opportunities Offered to Hancock, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    393.13
  - Bankruptcy of Reynolds Construction Corporation, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    390.7
  - American Security and Trust to Equipment Financing, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    389.3
  - Schultz Construction Corporation Insurance Problems, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    393.7
  - Insurance Coverage, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    390.4
  - Bonres, Bonner Reston, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    479.6
  - Glenvale Condominium Reston, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    479.7
  - Insurance for Reston (Approval of Dominion Mortgage), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    392.8
  - Foreclosure by Mount Vernon Bank on Charmark Corporation, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    393.10
- Series 5: Associations and Corporations, 1962-1968; (3 boxes)
  Series five is titled Association and Corporations with information from different organizations such as the Reston Home Owners Association. The series is stored in boxes 9 through 12.
  - Reston, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    209.5
  - Reston, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    209.6
  - Reston, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    209.4
  - Reston Bootle Club-The Quay Club, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    368.13
  - Reston Bottle Club-The Quay Club, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    369.1
  - Reston Bottle Club (Incorporated), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    369.2
  - Reston First Home Owners Association, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    367.8
  - Palindrome Corporation, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    209.3
  - Reston Bottle Club-The Quay Club, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Palindrome Corporation, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    209.2
  - Reston Home Owners Association (RHOA), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    373.3
  - Reston Home Owners Association, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    373.2
  - Notice Rights and Voting Rights of Reston's First Homeowners Association, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    372.9
  - Notice Rights and Voting Rights of Reston's First Home Owners' Association, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    372.10
  - Reston Virginia Foundation for Community Program, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    372.7
  - Conveyance from Mittleman and Restate to First Home Owners Association, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    378.3
  - Lakeview Mall Cluster Association-Incorporated, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    379.4
  - Palindrome Corporation, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    211.3
  - Palindrome Corporation, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    209.1
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    383.14
  - Minutes of Meeting of Board of Directors and Executive Committee, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    392.4
  - Charter Oak Associates, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    390.9
  - Charter Oak Associates, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    390.8
  - Merger of Home Owner Associations, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    388.2
  - Home Owners Association General Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    388.3
  - Governor's Square Cluster Association, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    388.1
  - Claims of J.W. Tolley and Associates, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    393.16
  - M and M Builders, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    390.11
- Series 6: Legal Files, 1965-1978; (4 boxes)
  Series six is Legal Files. The documents in this series are mostly information on different court cases that Edgar A. Prichard was working on behalf of Reston. The series is stored in boxes 12 through 16.
  - Unlawful Detainer, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    370.9
  - Deed of Extension North Shore Drive, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    370.8
  - Deed to Hickory Cluster Association, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    370.1
  - Deed to Waterview Cluster Association (Cluster Common Area), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    369.8
  - Raymond Burke vs. Palindrome Corporation, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    369.17
  - Discharge of Mechanics, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    371.10
  - Discharge of Mechanics, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    371.9
  - Mech Lien Shafter vs. Edward Allen Property, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    375.6
  - Lease with General Technologies Corporation, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    375.3
  - Reston Plaza, Incorporated vs. Howard Bradford, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    374.1
  - Garnishment: Noble Lumber vs. Allied Building Products, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    372.11
  - Incorporation of Wainwright Cluster Association, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    376.5
  - Landlord-Tenant (Distress for Rent-Mooring Restaurant and John W. Splan Jr.), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    376.3
  - Mech Lien: United Masonry, Incorporated vs. Eugene Simipson and Brothers, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    376.1
  - Robertshaw Controls Company vs. Quast United Heating Simpson and Reston, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    376.7
  - Model Deed of Easement Form, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    376.9
  - Damage Suit-Washington Gas Light Company vs. George H. Lewis, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    377.2
  - Second Closing, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    377.8
  - 60 Access Road Easement From Mail Association, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    378.10
  - Amend Lease with the Southland, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    378.13
  - Note Collection v. Milke J. Morfessis, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    378.14
  - Unlawful Detainer (stable) vs. Requitation, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    379.5
  - Second Closing, Scope and Legal File, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    381.2
  - Grazing Lease with Wm. M. Jennings, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    379.9
  - Requitation, Incorporation-Suit Seeking Injunction, specific performance and 10,000 dollars damages, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    379.6
  - Anti-Trust Suit v. Reston Air Condition Corporation, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    384.6
  - Unlawful Detainer Richard B. Forsberg, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    383.13
  - Defense of Suit on Assignment by United Plumbing and Heating to Noland Company, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    383.9
  - Unlawful Detainer v. Kursch, Veatch and Associates, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    383.10
  - Amendment of Equitable, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    382.11
  - Unlawful detainer, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    382.4
  - Bruce W. Churchill-Suit to Recover Monies on Real Estate Contract, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    381.6
  - Specific Performance vs. Hickory cluster Associates, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    384.5
  - Brick and File Corporation, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    387.1
  - Distress Warrant vs. Mrs. Marie Zicha, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    384.10
  - Defense-Debt on Open Account, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    384.8
  - Unlawful Detainer-Marcel R. Martin, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    389.12
  - Reded of 10' Bridle Path, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    390.3
  - America Security vs. Gulf Oil, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    389.1
  - Reston Air Conditioner Corporation vs. Harry J. Gudrun Donove, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    393.12
  - US District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia-Alexandria Division: American Security and Trust Company vs. Gulf Oil Corporation, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    393.20
  - David V. Hill, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    393.9
  - Unlawful Detainer v. Harry J. Donohve, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    1
  - Harry J. Donohue and Gudrun P. Donchoe, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    392.3
  - Rental Tools and Equipment Company, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    391.6
  - Lawfile-Brief, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    389.4
  - Appeal File: American Security and Trust vs. Gulf Oil, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    388.8
  - Transcript of Proceedings-American Security and Trust Company vs. Gulf Oil Corporation, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    394.01
  - US District Court for the Eastern District of Virginia-Alexandria Division, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    394.2
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated vs. Board of Supervisors Stipulations, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    210.4
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated vs. Board of Supervisors-Pleadings, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    210.2
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated vs Board of Supervisors-Pleadings, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    210.1
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated vs. Board of Supervisors-Pleadings, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    210.3
- Series 7: Contracts, 1964-1968; (3 boxes)
  Series seven is titled Contracts. The documents are contracts with different organizations, such as the Motoral and various others. The series is stored in boxes 16 through 19.
  - Lease to Harry J. and Gudrun Donohue, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    368.12
  - Termination of Elmer Durbin Contract, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    368.9
  - Agreement Regarding Storm Drainage, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    368.7
  - Contract with Catholic Church acres, Fairfax County, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    368.6
  - Loan From American Security, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    368.5